Lealo Dyigjeri

Full Stack Software Developer

Flushing, NY | (646)578-3908 | lediodylgjeri@gmail.com | GitHub | LinkedIn | Portfolio

Career Objective

My calling in life has been to help people. Coming from a law enforcement background I have had the pleasure to help many by wearing different hats. The experience I gained in problem solving will reflect in my software engineering career. Through technology, I want to continue my work by being involved with future projects that advance humanity.

SKILLS: Python, Javascript, ReactJS, ExpressJS, NodeJS, Mongoose, MongoDB, Django, Docker, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, Git and GitHub

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineering Fellow | General Assembly | Remote | AUG 2022 - NOV 2022

- Developed fully responsive front end applications using HTML, CSS, Javascript and ReactJS.
- Developed multiple full stack applications using MongoDB, EspressJS, ReactJS, NodeJS, Python, Django, Docker and PostgreSQL with full CRUD functionality.
- Managed team-based project using Git version control and GitHub.

Police Officer | NYPD | New York, NY | JULY 2015 - NOV 2021

- Conducted witness interviews and gathered details regarding incidents to determine best course of action.
- Demonstrate clear thinking in high-pressure environments.
- Conducted long term investigations into organized criminal groups with the Violent Crime Squad and Gang Squad.
- Gathered and disseminated raw intelligence for real-time analysis and decision-making.
- Maintained organized records of all information and material pertinent to open investigations.
- Prepared detailed criminal reports of evidence gathered and presented to District Attorney.
- Testified in court to present evidence or acted as a witness in traffic and criminal court.

Residential Concierge | Penmark Realty Corp. | New York, NY | FEB 2013 - JULY 2015

- Projected a consistent image that complemented the property appearance, performance, and service orientation, while ensuring property rules and regulations were enforced.
- Completed daily shift reports giving a time-stamped overview of what went on during the shift.
- Established relationships with residents to tailor services to their individual needs.
- Monitored fire alarm system and other mechanical equipment while building staff was not on duty.

Assistant Property Manager | The Moinian Group | New York, NY | MARCH 2011 - DEC 2012

- Assisted in managing the day-to-day operations of 6 commercial and residential buildings.
- Communicated with tenants regarding property related issues.
- Coordinated with outside vendors to arrange for maintenance, landscaping, security and other services needed.
- Responded to emergency calls and reported to property manager.

EDUCATION

General Assembly | Software Engineering Immersive | Remote

Masters of Arts in Criminal Justice | CUNY John Jay College | New York, NY